https://asset-technology.com/privacy-policy/

Qiyas
Meeting Management System (MMS)
Qiyas
Meeting Management System (MMS)
›
Home - Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyAt ASSET Technology Group we take your personal privacy very seriously. As a general rule, our website does not collect your personal information unless you choose to provide that information to us in a way that improves your experience and relationship with us. When you choose to provide us with your personal information, you are giving our website your permission to use that information for the stated purposes listed in this privacy policy. If you choose not to provide us with that information, it might limit the features and services that you can use on this website.Our website might request to collect these information:Contact or Request Demo FormsAd scripts running on any pages of our siteCookiesGenerally, the information requested by https://asset-technology.com will be used to provide a website feature or service to you, such as support, tailored content to your interests and an overall better customer experience.Privacy NoticeSome of the services on this website allow you to send us an email. We will use the information you provide, such as email address or phone number, only to respond to your inquiry. Keep in mind that email transmissions are not encrypted by default, so we suggest you do not send sensitive information such as social security numbers, credit card numbers, or bank account information via such contact forms.Website CookiesThis website collects and temporarily stores certain information about your visit to help us to better align our content and the website design with your needs. The information these cookies collect includes:The domain you access our website fromYour computer’s IP addressThe date and time you accessed the siteThe operating system of your computerThe browser you’re using to access our siteThe (URLs) of the pages you visit on our websiteThe URL of the site you came from, if you clicked a link there that brought you to our websiteWe may share this information internally with our website staff solely. This information is only used to improve the website and enhance our visitors’ experience. Raw data logs are only retained temporarily for site management purposes. ASSET Technology Group does not sell its customers’ e-mail addresses to third parties and e-mail addresses you provide are used only to service your account and provide you with information on ASSET products and services.
